[{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975045026,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":18544,"timeElapsed":181653},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975056763,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":11733,"timeElapsed":193390},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975064807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":8041,"timeElapsed":201433},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975068142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3334,"timeElapsed":204769},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975071523,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3378,"timeElapsed":208150},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975081166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":9642,"timeElapsed":217792},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975087647,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":6478,"timeElapsed":224274},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975100846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":13198,"timeElapsed":237473},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975106199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":5349,"timeElapsed":242826},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975115735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":7822,"timeElapsed":252361},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975117654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":1918,"timeElapsed":254281},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975119631,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":1975,"timeElapsed":256258},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975121262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":1630,"timeElapsed":257889},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975123390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2128,"timeElapsed":260017},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975125286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1895,"timeElapsed":261913},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975127047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":1758,"timeElapsed":263673},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975128614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1566,"timeElapsed":265241},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975132807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4191,"timeElapsed":269434},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975150718,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":16727,"timeElapsed":287345},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975157015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":6295,"timeElapsed":293642},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975159710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2694,"timeElapsed":296337},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975161534,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":1823,"timeElapsed":298161},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975163670,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2135,"timeElapsed":300297},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975167496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3825,"timeElapsed":304123},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975171286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3789,"timeElapsed":307913},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975183922,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":12635,"timeElapsed":320549},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975189095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":5169,"timeElapsed":325722},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975193302,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4205,"timeElapsed":329929},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975202334,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":7974,"timeElapsed":338961},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975210159,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7823,"timeElapsed":346786},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975214202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4042,"timeElapsed":350829},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975218027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3822,"timeElapsed":354654},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975219914,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":1887,"timeElapsed":356541},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975222342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2426,"timeElapsed":358969},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975225010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2666,"timeElapsed":361637},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975226939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":1927,"timeElapsed":363566},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975229175,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2235,"timeElapsed":365801},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975231303,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2126,"timeElapsed":367930},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975241210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8501,"timeElapsed":377837},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975243802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2592,"timeElapsed":380429},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975246155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2350,"timeElapsed":382782},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975248698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2542,"timeElapsed":385325},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975251523,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2822,"timeElapsed":388150},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975259018,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7494,"timeElapsed":395645},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975264546,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5527,"timeElapsed":401173},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975268234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":3687,"timeElapsed":404861},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975270562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2326,"timeElapsed":407189},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975278754,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":7022,"timeElapsed":415381},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975281491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2735,"timeElapsed":418117},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975286619,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5127,"timeElapsed":423246},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975289283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2662,"timeElapsed":425910},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975292194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2910,"timeElapsed":428821},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975294715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2518,"timeElapsed":431342},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975296771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2054,"timeElapsed":433398},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975298354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1582,"timeElapsed":434981},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975300627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2271,"timeElapsed":437254},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975316283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":14423,"timeElapsed":452910},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975322642,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":6358,"timeElapsed":459269},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975326338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3694,"timeElapsed":462965},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975328586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2246,"timeElapsed":465213},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975330874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2288,"timeElapsed":467501},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975339634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":8759,"timeElapsed":476261},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975344010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4374,"timeElapsed":480636},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975345890,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1878,"timeElapsed":482517},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975348922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3032,"timeElapsed":485549},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975384691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":34480,"timeElapsed":521318},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975386458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":1766,"timeElapsed":523085},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975388869,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2409,"timeElapsed":525496},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975390659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1787,"timeElapsed":527285},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975392629,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1968,"timeElapsed":529256},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975394356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1726,"timeElapsed":530983},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975396126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":1768,"timeElapsed":532753},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975398166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2038,"timeElapsed":534793},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975399966,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":1798,"timeElapsed":536593},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975406727,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5753,"timeElapsed":543354},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975409943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3214,"timeElapsed":546570},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975412826,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2883,"timeElapsed":549453},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975414527,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1699,"timeElapsed":551153},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975416506,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":1978,"timeElapsed":553133},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975418999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2489,"timeElapsed":555626},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975420623,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1623,"timeElapsed":557250},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975422422,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1797,"timeElapsed":559049},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975424259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1835,"timeElapsed":560886},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975432062,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6807,"timeElapsed":568689},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975435455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3390,"timeElapsed":572082},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975437782,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2327,"timeElapsed":574409},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975439885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2102,"timeElapsed":576512},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975442078,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2192,"timeElapsed":578705},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975444455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2375,"timeElapsed":581082},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975446510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2055,"timeElapsed":583137},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975448519,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2006,"timeElapsed":585146},{"subjectID":"u2hv1ej0sw","prolificID":"6751fd6a50221edd2da8333e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7c13ce4861332cec73","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975451162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2643,"timeElapsed":587789}]